# K/A

# **Kyle Atterson**

# Technical and Design Expert

#### CONTACT

P: (812) 240-6873

**E:** kyle.atterson@twicry.com

A: Hymera, IN

L: linkedin.com/in/kvle-atterson/

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Indiana State University**

Bachelor of Science (May, 2020)

- Business Administration
- Information Technology
- Management Information Systems

Master of Science (May, 2022)

- Computer Science

## **SKILLS**

- Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, and XD
- Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, and Outlook
- Google Docs and Sheets
- HTML / CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, PHP, MySQL
- Java, C/C++, C#, Python
- Git
- Asana, JIRA, Wrike, ClickUp
- Project Management
- Web and Technical Design
- Creative and Technical Writing

### **RELATED**

- Part-time game designer, working with TTRPGs and products to create design contents and new, full systems.
- Community Management experience dealing with fostering activity across multiple chat programs, social media, and servers.

#### **SUMMARY**

A designer with a myriad of experience in modern coding and design programs. I bring a precise eye for detail and a vast knowledge of systems that allows me to create high quality design and technical work to specification. I also have experience in training new staff, working in group-oriented projects and scenarios, and have worked with developing web technology to ensure accessible usability and proper architecture.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Web Architect, Indiana State University

October 2021 - Present

- Lead web programmer for Drupal CMS in charge of user architecture and ensuring best practices.
- Established partnerships with the web team, campus constituents, and campus governance.
- Trains university staff and creates and provides training documents
- Lead the switch from Google Universal Analytics to GA4

### Freelance Web Developer & Marketer, various

December 2021 - Present

- Worked with multiplie people to create and maintain various web sites.
- Helped set up Google analytics, and write documentation for proper use.
- Generated multiple marketing plans for different products, and helped to ensure they happened.

Instructor, Indiana State University

August 2023 - Present

• Taught web programming to Undergraduates. CS-170

#### Systems Coordinator, Bursar Operations

August 2020 - October 2021

- Assisted with all technical aspects of Bursar Operations
- Charged with overcoming process failures with existing tasks, designing new, efficient processes.
- Day-to-day university-wide balancing tasks.

#### Lead Student Web Developer, University Marketing

August 2017 - August 2020

- Managed a team of 3 student developers to handle incoming tickets and resolve university-wide technique questions and issues.
- Promoted from to lead position after 2 years of dedicated work.
- Created basic documentation for training new student developers, including practices and operations.
- Implemented planned changes to the university website, including designing new or migrating sites